commerce.com.tw 2004-06-05

# Commerce.com.tw, trade, B2B , trade lead , E-commerce , manufacturer , machine , bicycle , handtool , autoparts,

**Our Commitment to Privacy**   
Taiwan Commerce respects the privacy of your information. Our Privacy Policy governs our online information practices and reflects our commitment to protect your privacy. 

**Security Measures  
**Your ID and password and profile description are protected. We suggested that you do not reveal your password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. Remember to log out of your account and close your browser window when you have finished your session. No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. As a result, while we try to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. 

**The Information  
**We Collect At the time you register for the services provided on our website, you would be required to provide information such as your name, address, phone number, company name and address and other personally-identifying information. We need this information to provide services that you request and to let you know of additional services about which you might be interested. We may also use this information to customize your experience in using our website. Taiwan Commerce is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We attempt to keep this information, apart from whatever information is used to market your company to potential trading partners, private. Taiwan Commerce does reserve the right to cooperate with law enforcement inquires and other third parties to enforce laws, intellectual property and other rights when, in its sole discretion, it believes in good faith such information is required to assist such parties. 

**Public Access to Information  
**The information you provide will be made available to all users of our website. Please remember that any information you disclose becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personally-identifying information. 

**Disclosure of Information  
**We have the right to disclose your information where we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing (or threatening to infringe) or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our title, rights, interests or property or those of other website users or of anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We also reserve the rights to disclose, without notice to you, personal information in response to a subpoena or other judicial order or when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is required by any law, regulation or listing requirement or by any stock/securities exchange, governmental or regulatory authority 

**Co-Branded Relationships  
**We have established relationships with other parties to offer you the benefit of other products and services which we ourselves do not offer. We offer you access to these other parties either through the use of hyperlinks to their sites from our website, or through offering "co-branded" sites in which both ourselves and these other parties share the same URL, domain name or pages within a domain name on the Internet. The Privacy Policy of such other parties may differ from ours. We therefore encourage you to read that policy before responding of any offers, products or services provided by such other parties. 

**Cookies  
**Taiwan Commerce may set and access cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a webserver and stored on your computer's hard drive. 

**Changes to Privacy Policy  
**Taiwan Commerce may modify this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages or direct mail. Correcting Your Information  
If you intend to change your information or data on our website, please contact
